









Pham Minh Phuc IT Expert

3 20/02

Qy Male

flashphuc219@gmail.com

District 6, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

. 0906686281

SUMMARY

♦ I am a passionate about new technologies and can sit for hours in front of my screen to watch how them were made. Punctuality person, plan out before what I'll do or targets were assigned. On my desk, I always have a small calendar in which I can note the date of meeting, deadlines. Hoping with a little experience in the web programming field (front-end) and deployments, I can contribute to the development of your company.

EDUCATION

07/2020 - 02/2021

Cybersoft - Cyberlearn Programing Education Center



- ◆ Programming course: thinking in programming, problem-solving, Java language, OOP
- ◆ Front-end Foundation course: basic knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SASS/SCSS, Javascript (ES5/ES6), Jquery, AJAX, Git, ...

02/2017 - 06/2017

VnPro Center



- ♦ I had knowledge about Networking(LAN, WAN, Wifi...)
- ♦ I was teached and contacted with devices of Cisco (Router, Switch...)

09/2011 - 09/2016

Ton Duc Thang University



- ♦ Major: Telecommunication
- ♦ Total score: 6.51.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2021 - 08/2022

Joint Stock Company Truong Hai Group



Technical Administrative Specialist(IT Helpdesk)

- ◆ Support users when experiencing problems with computer machinery (Win errors, machines not up, full mail, screen not up ...)
- ♦ Install computer equipment, necessary software (AutoCAD, Itax, HTKK, Nitro ...) for users, manage equipment, arrange and transport
- ◆ Do the paperwork handed over to users, direct events large and small are organized in conjunction with the event department
- ♦ Write a document instructing new personnel to use electronic devices, as well as internal installation
- ◆ Manage printer servers, create accounts for users, join domain, install mail, click network cables ...
- ◆ Support the difference department Employees. Create new accounts on the window server and Manage the operation of it and printing server. Checking group Mail and personal mail to reply

partner's issues (mail trouble, Install new software, printer, scan,...etc..).

◆ Creating the documents For new eployees or new softwares, solutions, devices. Setup meeting room (offline or online) for head officers Sometimes I supplied the infrastructure department (clean and Organize server room) Remote the peer's device by damware or ultraviewer for fixing Errors.

5/2021 - 11/2021

Alpha Apparel Group Corporation



Operation Expert(IT Helpdesk)

- ♦ Installation, maintennance, hardware clean. Follow operation system, setup software(Camera, AI, Corel...)
- ◆ Taking the network system are been operated fluently. If system is been taken break-down, will report suppliers to support right now. Suggesting the new configuration's PC or laptop to departments. Contacting the suppliers to supply products and hand over.

8/2019 - 3/2021



IT Employee

- ♦ Onsite in the Coopmart and support customers and colleagues about the company's software, hardware, server, cash...
- ◆ Fix and update the company's software, hardware, server, cash...

8/2017 - 2/2019

Dcorp R-Keeper Vietnam - Ho Chi Minh City

Deployment Employee and Command Center



- ♦ Deploy POS software(R-keeper7) for customers: Redsun, Golden Gate, New Pearl...
- ♦ Answer the questions about the software on the hotline. Support and solve by TeamViewer or ultra viewer about the software's bugs. if I solve impossibly, I'll onsite to the customers(with the condition include the customer sign technology contract)

08/2016 - 11/2016

FPT Shop - Ho Chi Minh City (FRT)

Support Technology And Sale



♦ Support Technology for the customer and sell items in the shop.

♦ Check products, software, date experience, licenses...

♦ Solve customer's incidents (the black screen, the battery is been failed, the speaker is inactive...)

CERTIFICATIONS / LICENSES

02/2017 - 06/2017

♦ CCNA Certification (Cisco Certified Network

Associate) (Vnpro, Ho Chi Minh City)

03/2016

◆ TOEIC 505 (IIG, Ho Chi Minh City)

SKILSS

Front-end Developer ♦ HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Git, React...

Microsoft Office

♦ Word, Excel, Power Point...

English

♦ Communicating (Intermediate), reading documents, writing email

Soft skills

♦ Teamwork, self study